







xuanbuithanh221@gmail.com



Bac Tu Liem, Ha Noi



0326 977 221



ttps://klpod221.github.io/

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

BKACAD Academy of Technology 2019 - 2022

SKILLS

Linux System Administrator

Linux, Bash, Prometheus, Grafana, MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Redis, Nginx, Apache.

Full-Stack Web Developer

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, NextJs, NodeJS, ExpressJS, VueJs, NuxtJS, PHP, Laravel, WordPress, Spring Boot, AngularJS.

DevOps

Git, GitLab, GitHub, GitLab Cl/CD, Jenkins, Docker, AWS.

Bui Thanh Xuan

Linux System Administrator

ABOUT

Summary

I have 1.5 year of experience in Linux System Administrator and 2 year of experience in Full-Stack Web Developer. I am a hard-working person, willing to learn new things, and always try my best to complete the assigned tasks.

Languages

English: Intermediate

EXPERIENCE

Linux System Administrator

Hachinet Software

04/2022 - Present

- Install, configure, and maintain Linux, BSD servers (Ubuntu, CentOS, FreeBSD) with Nginx, Apache web servers, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis databases.
- Install, configure, and maintain Docker servers; monitoring servers (Prometheus, Grafana); CI/CD servers (GitLab CI/CD), Git servers (GitLab); Mattermost servers.
- Install, configure, and maintain NAS servers (Synology).

Full-Stack Web Developer

Hachinet Software

04/2022 - Present

 Develop and maintain web applications using ReactJS, NextJS, NuxtJS, PHP, Laravel, WordPress.

Full-Stack Web Developer

Freelancer and Open Source

02/2022 - 05/2022

Work as a freelancer and open source contributor.

Full-Stack Web Developer

FPT Telecom

12/2021 - 02/2022

Design and develop web applications using Angular JS and Spring Boot.

PROJECTS

Hachinet System

Hachinet Software 08/2022 - Present

- Role: Linux System Administrator
- Team size: 2 members
- Install, configure, and maintain Linux, BSD servers (Ubuntu, CentOS, FreeBSD) with Nginx, Apache web servers, PostgreSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis databases.
- Install, configure, and maintain Docker servers; monitoring servers (Prometheus, Grafana); CI/CD servers (GitLab CI/CD), Git servers (GitLab); Mattermost servers.
- Install, configure, and maintain NAS servers (Synology).

Devworks, Devwork

Hachinet Software 04/2022 - Present

- Role: Full-Stack Web Developer
- Team size: 10 members
- Continuously develop and maintain the website using NuxtJS for Frontend and Laravel for Backend.

Hatonet

Hachinet Software 04/2022 - Present

- Role: Full-Stack Web Developer
- Team size: 10 members
- Continuously develop and maintain the website using NuxtJS for Frontend and Laravel for Backend.

ESS

Hachinet Software 04/2023 - 07/2023

- Role: Full-Stack Web Developer, DevOps
- Team size: 4 members
- Build the interface of the website according to the customer's design and develop new features using NuxtJS for Frontend and Laravel for Backend.
- Deploy the website on the CentOS server with Nginx, and MySQL.

The New Otani

Hachinet Software 02/2023 - 05/2023

- Role: Frontend Web Developer, Project Leader, DevOps
- Team size: 5 members
- Rebuild the interface of the website according to the customer's design and develop new features using Typo3 CMS.
- Setup the FreeBSD server with Nginx, PHP-FPM, and deploy the website on it.

AQAcademy

Hachinet Software 01/2023 - 01/2023

- Role: Web Developer, Project Leader
- Team size: 4 members
- Build the interface of the website according to the customer's design and develop new features using WordPress.

Kanzaki

Hachinet Software 10/2022 - 10/2022

- Role: Web Developer, Project Leader
- **Team size:** 4 members
- Build the interface of the website according to the customer's design and develop new features using WordPress.

Medon - Medlatec

Hachinet Software 06/2022 - 10/2022

- Role: Web Developer
- Team size: 2 members
- Build the interface of the website according to the customer's design and develop new features using NextJS.

Social Book

FPTTelecom 12/2021 - 02/2022

- Role: Full-Stack Web Developer
- Team size: 2 members
- Design and develop the website using AngularJS and Spring Boot as a backend.
- Develop real-time features using WebSocket.